pickmeupnews.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy -

**Pick Me Up News Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers the Pick Me Up News Website. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Ownership of Information**  
Pick Me Up News is the sole owner of the information collected on the Pick Me Up News website.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Pick Me Up News website, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Pick Me Up News does not endorse these comments as they are opinions of users not associated with Pick Me Up News or its employees.

**Mailing List**  
Pick Me Up News may launch a mailing list for Pick Me Up News. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Public Forums & Comments**  
This site makes chat rooms, message boards and comments available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Pick Me Up News has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Pick Me Up News only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on Pick Me Up News are delivered to users by third party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Pick Me Up News may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Pick Me Up News.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Pick Me Up News goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, user personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
Pick Me Up News contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Pick Me Up News is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Pick Me Up News

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Pick Me Up News changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Contact Details:**
